Good morning, I was
in Dare around 70 points but Smarty Trade got out,
net net, there was consolidation yesterday, if I
look at the closing basis,
Nifty started today and ended at the same point,
red light raj also got consolidation time,
less shame, this is also getting concerted in Dare, let me
show you a look,
everything has come closer, from the lows made in October,
they have achieved a rally of 20-20%, the
stock has achieved up to 50, 60, 70%, so
yesterday was an important day, there was a
great rally for it and there is a lot of
confusion among the analysts there,
I have just posted a article, its
title is King Kartavya Vimud, meaning
you are not able to understand anything, you have become completely confused,
you are starting to understand something, what is happening,
you are not able to understand anything,
someone is doing it, there is a boom,
someone has got the market done, they are
buying in the middle, this is going on and all the
big people are there in it  So in the meantime,
you should read the market and that
reading tells you every day that the undertone is
becoming very bad and there is a lot of bullishness and people are buying.
Till yesterday, we were always relieved that
now slowly, bullishness has started forming in other stocks as well. So,
one gentleman and the
name of the registration has also been changed.
He has read out very interesting names and
I will tell you that he has told you that
now in the non-recession
market, there is a little problem due to the rates. The
underlying asset is very good,
as it should have happened. This time the recession has been made a
little different. This brother from Apollo Global
Management, who said this,
Hero One sir, so I have
written this that people have spread confusion,
but the market is moving upwards.
Some support came from tea yesterday also
because China has been saying that we
can give stimulus. It has
asked all its banks for rate cut. So after looking at yesterday, you should
understand that there is a bullishness in the market as well. There were
no such signs which would make the market
gear up and now all the parts have come out
that announcements are being made, so that is why we have
tightened it. If the
pitch is weak, then there will be difficulty in front.  It is going to be
difficult for the team, the
level playing field is such that the
stock that is kept, Maruti Suzuki
India, had mentioned it yesterday as well, nothing is there, it is
showing a good move today, but if the date is
given today, then the stock can also get connected, so it is
not like that, we will watch out, we are enjoying yesterday's date,
yesterday it was 1.5% stronger,
Maruti Suzuki was mentioning this yesterday morning
that preparations are being made for the launch of Gemini,
yesterday there was a conviction that today it should have a
good face before the launch,
Gemini was planned today, but the event is to be played out,
now how is the biography, what is it, I have dreamt about it, I
just don't know
what is the pricing, in pricing I know
that they want to put it against Thar, they
want to pitch it, Thar has come to Jim,
all the variants are between 10 to 12 15 lakhs, is the
pricing of Zindagi around this
and how does Jimmy actually stand up,
Thar Visa also in terms of features,
you will have to watch out for all this, but this is an
attempt to make a position in the space of SV and  This way
forward, some from Brezza, some
Grand Vitara were already in the portfolio,
now this one more SUV Jimmy will be
seen added to it, then it will boost their SUV portfolio,
then the other one, do not go into it, do not go into the next stock which
I had sent, I am
not buying that, what did I say, keep three
news items on the
screen, what do you do
because your news will not be there today,
brother, the circuit filter was till yesterday, till 5th,
today it has become till 20th, from today that circuit
filter has been revised, we were consolidating it, we will make it a
little longer and wider, we were
consolidating it well for the whole year.  I keep
it green. Circuit filter
provides do not change anything but the thing is that
after a little consolidation it will move again
because sentiments improve.
What do traders like? They think the
matter will not get stuck. Perhaps I kept it green on this news at 5%. It is a
little risky. Keep in mind that
some global company said something that their
business will fall, so we all got scared and came to our senses
and we have targeted IIT. Here I am keeping
Wipro in green. Wipro had
recovered in intraday.
Keep the internet chart in a good way. There was 1% pressure
but there was recovery from the people.
Now here they launched one
yesterday. The market band news was that
Microsoft launched a new suite of
banking financial services on cloud.
After this band happened, there was another
interesting news which has already come and now keep in
mind that you will have to keep an eye on the
buyback of Rs 12000 crore which was
issued through tender route at Rs 445. Its record date is now coming out, the
date was given.  On June 16,
however, it will depend on the level of people's seat connection with Wipro. If you
want to accumulate it, you can buy it at a
price of ₹445. Bye Bye Surendra, even then
I
think Wipro will definitely become a downward side
support. This is coming close to the record date.
Wipro has turned green, there are
three over Green
Power. They have signed an agreement with the Maharashtra government. There is a
capacity of 5700 MW,
so these three will be executed in the next 5 years.
This 3000 MW plant will be installed in Karjat near Mumbai. One will be installed
in Maval and the other in June. All these
three are for the periphery only.
Around Rs 27,000 crore will be
spent on this project, all three together, and
it has to be executed in the next 5 years. It is a
very big contract, so I
think Empower should be kept on the side.
IFB Industries has been taken
because Societe Generale has bought three lakh
shares in it.  If it is trading at ₹800 and is trading at ₹802, then
they bought it, it is
around this price, so it is possible that they may
tweet green. There were many updates about Star Health Generation regarding
their business,
their premium has grown by 16% in the last
10 years and
they are doing
very well in health insurance compared to the market. If you
look at other big people as well, then
I Ashish will be in your team, instead of
live, people should focus more on health insurance,
which was becoming the
second best in their team in Star, so I
included Star
for general insurance, the premium in other stocks is
industry leading, growth of 21% is
also to be kept in mind, before this out
organized, I have enjoyed a very good mood, mention it
here, the auto
NCRS which I was talking about, but all these
auto N series stocks are in a very bullish mood,
now before the launch of Ginni and the
rise in Maruti's own stock,
this will make you watch out in the space, now I will
look at this and I was looking at many Maruti's suppliers
etc., it
is affordable.  It has been
kept green. Yesterday evening, an update came that their
subsidiary
is preparing to launch an idea of
1 crore 16 lakh equity shares which will be
listed on BSE NSC. The
proposal for value and locking is being worked out. There are
three people again. Hey, in the next three months,
steel companies have been taken over - Tata Steel and
GSPL. See, the news is very simple
that there have been two big developments from China due to
which there is a possibility of a boom in metals. What
we had told you the day before yesterday that there will be a
big boom in metals, that was the news. A
revival has been seen from China. Now the news is coming out
that firstly, the state
government, state, does not mean state, the
entire country can be called a state,
so they have asked their banks to
cut rates, especially to help the real estate sector. So, this is
a very
big decision. At a time when
many countries across the world are troubled due to rates,
rates are being cut in China, so its benefit is being seen
there. That is why metals are going up. The
prices of iron and steel had continuously gone up and were
excellent from there.  Recovery was seen. The
second big decision
could be the announcement of a stimulus. It
could be for the real estate sector because they were the ones who
created the most problems there.
Due to these two news,
we feel that a big boom will be seen in the metal stocks again
today like it happened the day before yesterday. So
understand one thing here, the
channel has taken a very big decision that the
rate of dollar is being cut, due to which many
people who had made reserves by sitting and doing audio, will
come out, then there will be more
benefit from it and the problems of the youth who were in trouble will be
solved. So, it seems that all these decisions will lead to a
boom in the metal and keep all the three
stocks here in the steel ones. Rest of the
stocks are kept. A
small break and after the break, the next judge
private
[Music]
[Music] [
Music]
10 years
[Music]
[Music] I have
taught by holding the fingers of the fingers, I have placed the
order and there are some
more operations
[Music]
Speaking in your language,
just see which Alexa of every part has come
daily from tomorrow
[Music]
My heart has found a way to reach every heart  We have
built it
together in 10 years and have reached many heights. Right now we have just
expanded it a little bit.
Together we have built our shop
[Music] We have
built it
[Music]
Incomplete because with gold you have the power to
take big decisions. To
balance risk and returns
[Music] The
power to buy and sell easily. That is why
gold is your strategy's wanted,
without which your portfolio is incomplete. The
power of gold also makes your portfolio incomplete.
How many more rounds will you have to make to the World Gold Council?
Sir, please take
care of us, we will take care of you.
[Music] Till now
more than 300 corrupt people have been arrested.
Bribe takers are in trouble
now in Punjab. I want to give this message to the people of Punjab that
making Punjab corruption free is not our promise but our guarantee. [
Music]
[Praise]
[Music]
[Music] There is
a report by Motilal Oswal, they have given a
target of 2890. The string behind this is that
they have given that it is from structural oil
because in the previous six months,
hiring in IT had reduced a lot. There was a
lot of pressure on them, margins had
fallen, so there was no growth,
but now they feel that all those  These are forgotten
things of the past and now the way the
economy revival is being seen
in India, it has started with hiring, so
this growth will be seen in a good way, they have given it a race,
they believe that the
EPF to 2025 will
see good growth here, there is a medium P of 5 air, in
front of that the stock is currently trading at a 10% discount,
this question has been resolved with concession,
tomorrow the cost of the project will be fixed, till then the road,
nowadays such news has
given a target of 800 and they say
that the following can surprise you on the
positive side and the growth of housing will
add 18-20%,
they are counting a lot of things in this, they
believe that it can go much higher from here,
so we can pay attention to it and this is the 10th stock,
after a long time an actual
report has come and they have
kept a target of 325, it is running from ₹2627, it is
above 300 rupees, their gradual
tick is the margin  Improvements are taking place and the
volume is starting to come from the economy,
so the entire picture that is forming, there
is a report on ITC as well for all these companies, so it is better for all these,
our corporate
learning people are transferring the news, before that some action is being taken,
this stock is already running, you keep it running today
because tomorrow there is an accident, today the profit
takers might accumulate, so
before that let's see, it is consolidating, the
stock giving exactly, it was consolidating yesterday as well,
after that, the day before yesterday it happened, 9th,
keep Bhansali Engineering Polymers adopted
brother, this stock is increasing and I will
tell you the reason behind the increase, the day after tomorrow is the ex-date, there is a
special of ₹14 and a final dividend of ₹1, a
dividend of ₹15 is to come, the stock is trading at
165, that is why it is increasing because even after trading, it is trading
at 165, 165 means a dividend of 9%,
if I had bought the
stock today, friend, I had missed out on 3 good months.  Whatever
charts show for the month, you will understand how the
last one is continuously getting affected
before the ex-date of its dividend and Infosys is
only going green. So
many stocks are trading in the green yesterday. Today, a little break is visible in the green.